center7.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy - Data Bank

### OUR COMMITMENT

DataBank Holdings, Ltd. understands the importance of privacy in today’s world. DataBank Holdings, Ltd. is committed to protecting the privacy of our website visitors and clients. We uphold the highest industry standards in online privacy. This Privacy Statement discloses our privacy practices and expresses our commitment to keeping you informed of the information we collect and how it is used. This Statement applies to all personal information we handle in connection with our website. This statement sets forth our information gathering and dissemination practices for the [**www.databank.com**](https://www.databank.com/) and related websites. We will not disclose information about customers or users without express permission unless the release of said information is required by government subpoena. DataBank Holdings, Ltd. reserves the right to modify our statement at any time. The most current version of the privacy statement will always be available at http://www.databank.com/privacy/.

#### GDPR / EU-U.S. PRIVACY SHIELD

DataBank Holdings, Ltd. (“DataBank”) adheres and complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and GDPR. DataBank is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield site (<https://www.privacyshield.gov/> ), and to view the Privacy Shield List, please see <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

DataBank is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework. DataBank complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, DataBank is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. Individuals may access their personal data, and may contact us at [compliance@databank.com](mailto:compliance@databank.com) to resolve any complaints regarding our collection or use of your personal data, or to limit the use or disclosure of any personal data. In certain situations, DataBank may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, DataBank Holdings, Ltd. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact DataBank Holdings, Ltd. Compliance at: [compliance@databank.com](mailto:compliance@databank.com).

DataBank Holdings, Ltd. commits to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by the panel with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship and for unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield>

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website [<https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>], You may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

#### WHAT WE COLLECT

Our sites use several different forms that our customers can use to request information, products, and services. From these forms, we collect the following information:

  * Visitors’ contact information (such as e-mail addresses, name, telephone, number, and postal address)
  * Unique identifiers (such as customer numbers)
  * Financial information (such as credit card numbers)
  * IP addresses

#### WE USE CERTAIN GOOGLE ADVERTISING PRODUCTS

We have implemented Google advertising products to display advertising on our website. These products collect traffic data using a specific cookie placed on your computer by Google. In addition we use “Remarketing with Google Analytics” to advertise online.

#### HOW SECURE IS THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

DataBank Holdings, Ltd. makes every effort to follow industry standard security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All financial information is encrypted during transmission and our company databases are accessible only to internal employees.

#### WHAT DO WE USE THIS INFORMATION FOR?

**Contact Information**  
We use your contact information to send you information about our company, process requests for services, send invoices, and to contact you when necessary. We also use the information we collect to improve the content of our website. You will not receive any communications from us unless you opt-in to communications from DataBank or an DataBank business partner. Non-Customers may opt-out of communications. Existing customers cannot opt-out of receiving information that we deem important for us to communicate in order to provide ongoing services and support. Customers can update their contact information via the support portal.

**Financial Information**  
We may ask you to enter your credit card or bank account information on our websites to enable us to charge your account when you purchase servers or services from us. All information you will be asked to enter is protected using strong encryption techniques. We collect this information on a transaction-by-transaction basis and will never authorize the release of this information to anyone not directly involved in processing the transaction. This information may be encrypted and stored for logging purposes.

**IP addresses**  
We may use your unique network address (IP address) to help diagnose problems with our services, and to administer our website.

**Cookies**  
We use cookies to keep track of your purchases during the time you view [www.databank.com](https://www.databank.com/). We may also use them to recognize return visitors and to track our promotions. DataBank Holdings, Ltd. may collect personally identifiable information from visitors in several ways, such as online forms but only when visitors volunteer such information. DataBank Holdings, Ltd. may also collect information about how visitors interact with our website. This information is obtained through analysis of server logs and the use of “cookies” placed on user machines. A cookie is a piece of software that a web server can store on a computer system to identify the visitor if they visit the website again. All of the information that we collect from visitors through the use of cookies is not personally identifiable. However, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that visitors provide us through our website. We gather this information for internal use only and will never authorize the release of this information to anyone outside of DataBank Holdings, Ltd.

#### Use of Google Products

You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the advertising displayed by following this [link](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Third-party vendors, including Google, use the cookies placed on your computer in conjunction with their technology to show you advertising even when you are not on our site. These cookies and analytical tools record the sites you visit and other information regarding your activity on the Internet and display advertising based upon that information.

You may opt-out of certain aspects of the Google products by clicking [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) (https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated).

#### Information Disclosure

DataBank Holdings, Ltd. will not disclose information about customers or a visitor without the express permission of the customer unless the release of this information is required to satisfy an action requested by the customer or is required by a government or law enforcement subpoena. However, we reserve the right to transfer information collected from our customers in connection with any future transaction involving the transfer of the assets of our company.

#### QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

**Information Review or Change  **  
If you desire to review or change your personally identifiable information held by DataBank Hosting, please contact us at [compliance@databank.com](mailto:compliance@databank.com). We do not respond to anonymous correspondence and will refer individuals who deliberately attempt to mislead us regarding their identity to appropriate law enforcement officials.

**Notice of Changes to the Privacy Policy  **  
Changes to this Privacy Policy may be made by DataBank at our discretion and will be published to the website, [http://www.databank.com](https://www.databank.com/).

Please contact us with any questions regarding the DataBank Holdings, Ltd. privacy statement at:

Telephone: (214) 720 – 2266  
Email: [compliance@databank.com](mailto:compliance@databank.com)  
Postal Address: DataBank Holdings, Ltd.  
400 South Akard Street  
Suite #100  
Dallas, TX  75202  
Attention: Compliance
